# Guilherme Branco Stracini

Mobile phone: +55 (11) 97265-9788

E-mail: guilherme@guilhermebranco.com.br
Website: https://guilherme.stracini.com
Blog: https://blog.guilhermebranco.com.br
GitHub: https://github.com/guibranco

Updated at 23th April 2020

### **Professional Summary**

Well experienced with C# and JS (both, front and backend via NodeJS), working with e-commerce, integrations, web and desktop solutions since 2012.

I have also worked with PHP since 2007 for freelance jobs.

Working over years, building integrations between systems (Zendesk, VTEX, SAP, Sankhya, Adyen, MaxiPago) and developing video content platforms (Canal do Artesanato, Vitrine do Artesanato), booking application (EVNT).

Currently working in a API banking / Open banking projects, with .NET Core using DDD architecture and SOLID principles for a digital bank em São Paulo, Brazil.

#### Core Qualifications / Soft Skills

- C# .NET Framework / .NET Core MVC, WebAPI, WCF, Windows Forms, SignalR
- Entity Framework / Entity Framework Core / Dapper ORM
- JS / NodeJS Express, HAPI, REST API, Jobs, Scheduler
- PHP Code Igniter
- SQL DBMS SQL Server, Oracle 12c, MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL
- noSQL technologies Redis, Elastic Search, MongoDB
- Messaging/Queue RabbitMQ
- DevOps culture
- Front end technologies HTML5, CSS3, JS, BootStrap, Vue, Angular, jQuery, React, Materialize
- Cloud platform AWS S3, AWS EC2, AWS Route 53, AWS ELB, Azure, Heroku
- CI/CD TeamCity, AppVeyor, Jenkins, TFS
- VCS GIT / SVN GitHub, BitBucket, Visual SVN
- Agile culture Kanban, Scrum
- Agile Project Management Jira, TFS, Trello
- SOLID, DDD and BDD
- Docker & Kubernetes
- Teams management up to 5 developers
- Learning Rust and Python

#### Work Experience

#### Banco BS2 (K2 Partnering - consulting)

(financial services | +2k employees)

Software Engineer / .NET Developer

Period: Jul/2019 - Now

- Implementation of PIX (Instantly payments BACEN)
- Development of API banking product (<u>https://devs.bs2.com</u>) <u>BaaS</u>
- Development of open banking project
- Development of APIs using .NET Core, Dapper, Entity Framework and DDD
- Deploy and development using Docker containers
- Supporting clients in integration process

#### C&A Modas (Foco em Você - consulting)

(fashion company | +16k employees Brazil / +50k employees worldwide)

System Analyst / Backend Developer / Fullstack Developer

Period: Dec/2018 – Jun/2018 (7 months)

- Development of integrations solutions using Zendesk, SAP, Oracle and other internal systems
- · Automation of payment/refund process using Adyen gateway
- · Automation of process using .NET Core
- Develop new features and APIs using NodeJS (Express & HAPI)
- Develop of an unified library in .NET Core to be used internally by all teams, with commons & utils needs

### Editora Inovação / Inovação Media Group

(content producer / online retail seller | +100 employees)

**Development Coordinator** 

Period: Jan/2016 - Nov/2018 (3 years)

- Coordinate/support third party associates
- Deploy SOLID principles in projects
- Implement and evangelize CI/CD methodologies
- Development of integrations solutions
- Development of REST APIs for mobile apps
- Coordinate the development of a CRM system
- DevOps culture

#### Editora Inovação / Inovação Media Group

(content producer / online retail seller | +100 employees)

Software Development Analyst

Period: Nov/2013 - Dec/2015 (2 years)

- Development of REST APIs and MVC projects using .NET stack
- Integration with VTEX (REST API and SOAP WebService)
- Integration with payment gateway (MaxiPago)
- Management of triggers and procedures in SQL Server databases
- Disaster management and automated backup plans for SQL Server / Windows service and Amazon Web Services (AWS)

### Editora Inovação / Inovação Media Group

(content producer / online retail seller | +50 employees)

IT Analyst / Jr Developer

Period: Nov/2012 - Oct/2013 (1 year)

- Development of video portals using MVC with Microsoft stack
- Planning, modeling, implementation and process documentation ERP
- Requirements gathering
- Monitoring and management of SQL Server

# Editora Inovação / Inovação Media Group

(content producer / online retail seller | +50 employees)

Internship - IT

Period: Nov/2011 - Oct/2012 (1 year)

- Development of e-mails marketings
- Formatting, maintenance and installation of micro-computers(Windows and Linux Ubuntu)
- General software installation and configuration

   Development of evictors (VR NET) for manager
- Development of system (VB.NET) for management of digital PBX (Total IP)
- Development of new features, tools and bug fixes in existing projects (classic ASP and PHP)

## Freelancer

Developer / Analyst / Consultant

Period: 2007 – Now

- Acting as an independent consultant for some companies that integrate with VTEX (e-commerce platform)
- One-off jobs, as a freelancer, using C #, PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS and also JS for frontend
- Building integrations between systems using C#

# Education

FATEC São Caetano do Sul - Antônio Russo - Analysis and systems development - Technologiet

Technologist Period: 2011-2015

## Certificates

**SENAC** - Computer technician

Duration (hours): 1000 Period: 2009-2011

CNA - English

Duration (hours): 240 Period: 2005-2009

SOS Computadores - Computer assembly & maintenance and network course

Duration (hours): 78

Period: 2005

Languages	
	Portuguese - Native
	English - Fluent
	Spanish - Basic